let savollar14 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "apprentice",
      answer: "A. shogird",
      options: [
        "A. shogird",
        "B. o'qituvchi",
        "C. ustoz",
        "D. boshliq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to assure",
      answer: "B. ishontirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. shubha qilmoq",
        "B. ishontirmoq",
        "C. aldamoq",
        "D. to'xtatmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bandage",
      answer: "C. bint",
      options: [
        "A. doka",
        "B. kiyim",
        "C. bint",
        "D. qaychi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to bleed",
      answer: "D. qon ketmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tuzalmoq",
        "B. jarohatlamoq",
        "C. yopmoq",
        "D. qon ketmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to bond",
      answer: "B. do'stlashmoq",
      options: [
        "A. urishmoq",
        "B. do'stlashmoq",
        "C. ajralmoq",
        "D. unutmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "chef",
      answer: "A. oshpaz",
      options: [
        "A. oshpaz",
        "B. ofitsiant",
        "C. menejer",
        "D. rahbar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "crown",
      answer: "D. toj",
      options: [
        "A. shlyapa",
        "B. dubulg'a",
        "C. ro'mol",
        "D. toj"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "departure",
      answer: "A. jo'nab ketish",
      options: [
        "A. jo'nab ketish",
        "B. kelish",
        "C. kutish",
        "D. qarshi olish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "diligent",
      answer: "B. mehnatkash",
      options: [
        "A. dangasa",
        "B. mehnatkash",
        "C. parishon",
        "D. zerikarli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "emperor",
      answer: "C. imperator",
      options: [
        "A. rahbar",
        "B. shoh",
        "C. imperator",
        "D. vazir"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "fiber",
      answer: "A. tola",
      options: [
        "A. tola",
        "B. sim",
        "C. ip",
        "D. mato"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "horrible",
      answer: "B. dahshatli",
      options: [
        "A. yoqimli",
        "B. dahshatli",
        "C. chiroyli",
        "D. quvnoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "impolite",
      answer: "D. odobsiz",
      options: [
        "A. muloyim",
        "B. mehribon",
        "C. e'tiborli",
        "D. odobsiz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to kneel",
      answer: "A. tiz cho'kmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tiz cho'kmoq",
        "B. yugurmoq",
        "C. tik turmoq",
        "D. sakramoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "luxury",
      answer: "B. hashamat",
      options: [
        "A. oddiylik",
        "B. hashamat",
        "C. muhtojlik",
        "D. arzonlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "massive",
      answer: "D. juda katta",
      options: [
        "A. kichik",
        "B. o'rta",
        "C. zaif",
        "D. juda katta"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to panic",
      answer: "C. vahimaga tushmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tinchlanmoq",
        "B. xursand bo'lmoq",
        "C. vahimaga tushmoq",
        "D. o'ylamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "priority",
      answer: "A. ustuvorlik",
      options: [
        "A. ustuvorlik",
        "B. e'tiborsizlik",
        "C. e'tiborsiz",
        "D. muhimlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "robe",
      answer: "B. xalat",
      options: [
        "A. ko'ylak",
        "B. xalat",
        "C. kostyum",
        "D. kamzul"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to scold",
      answer: "C. tanbeh bermoq",
      options: [
        "A. maqtamoq",
        "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
        "C. tanbeh bermoq",
        "D. mukofotlamoq"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
  export default savollar14;
  